<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tourist app</string>
    <string name="title_activity_choosen_image">choosenImage</string>
    <string name="univerza_name">UNIVERSITY OF LJUBLJANA</string>
    <string name="univerza_desc">The University of Ljubljana was founded in 1919 on the foundations of a long-established pedagogical tradition.</string>
    <string name="zvezda_name">KONGRESNI TRG SQUARE</string>
    <string name="zvezda_desc">The site of the present Kongresni trg square was occupied by a small square already back in the Baroque period.
        The original square was thoroughly reconstructed for the 1821 Congress of the Holy Alliance and named after it.</string>
    <string name="vodnik_name">VODNIK MONUMENT</string>
    <string name="vodnik_desc">Valentin Vodnik Monument, is dedicated to the Carniolan priest, poet and journalist Valentin Vodnik (1758−1819).
        It stands at Vodnik Square (Vodnikov trg) in Ljubljana, the capital of Slovenia, in the immediate vicinity of the Ljubljana Central Market.</string>
    <string name="grad_name">LJUBLJANA CASTLE</string>
    <string name="grad_desc">Ljubljana Castle, standing on a hill above the city for about 900 years, is Ljubljana\'s main attraction.
        The castle\'s Outlook Tower and ramparts offer some of the most beautiful views of the city, while the castle
        houses a museum exhibition on Slovenian history, a puppet museum, and a number of historical rooms such as the Chapel of St George,
        the Prison, and a video presentation room called Virtual Castle.</string>
    <string name="zmajski_name">DRAGON BRIDGE</string>
    <string name="zmajski_desc">The Dragon Bridge, adorned with famous dragon statues, appears in the most recognizable images of Ljubljana.
        If you haven\'t been photographed next to a Dragon Bridge dragon, you can hardly claim that you have visited Ljubljana.
        The four dragon statues, which look slightly terrifying and almost real (if, of course, you believe that dragons might be real),
        are a masterpiece which has been exciting imagination since the bridge was built.</string>
    <string name="nuk_name">NATIONAL AND UNIVERSITY LIBRARY</string>
    <string name="nuk_desc">The National and University Library, whose archives contain, among other things, a rich collection of medieval manuscripts,
        incunabula and Renaissance prints, was built between 1936 and 1941 to designs by Jože Plečnik.</string>
    <string name="presern_name">PREŠERNOV TRG SQUARE</string>
    <string name="presern_desc">The Prešernov trg square developed from a road junction in front of one of the city gates leading to medieval Ljubljana.
        Next to the junction, a Franciscan church of the Annunciation was built in the 17th century,
        but the junction was turned into a square and paved only after the city walls were pulled down in the middle of the 19th century.</string>
    <string name="mestna_name">TOWN HALL</string>
    <string name="mestna_desc">Ljubljana\'s Town Hall (locally referred to as Mestna hiša, Magistrat or Rotovž), is used as the seat of the Municipality of Ljubljana.
        It was built in the late 15th century by the master builder Peter Bezlaj. It assumed its present appearance between 1717 and 1719, when an
        annexe designed by Carlo Martinuzzi was added to it by the master builder Gregor Maček Snr. Later the building was alterated several times,
        the most thoroughly by the architect Svetozar Križaj in 1963.</string>
    <string name="franciskanska_name">FRANCISCAN CHURCH</string>
    <string name="franciskanska_desc">The Franciscan Monastery and the Church of the Annunciation are the two buildings contributing most significantly to the
        appearance of the Prešernov trg square, the central square in Ljubljana.
        Until the end of the 18th century, the monastery was the home of Augustine monks.</string>
    <string name="robbov_name">ROBBA FOUNTAIN</string>
    <string name="robbov_desc">The Robba Fountain, one of Ljubljana\'s best known Baroque monuments, also known as The Fountain of Three Carniolan Rivers," +
        " stands at the edge of the Mestni trg square. It was created between 1743 and 1751</string>
</resources>
